Contact

nzuri13.yw@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/yolandarhodes-rn-bsn-crrn-25381570 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Admissions
Brain Injury Rehabilitation
Spinal Cord Injury

Certifications
CRRN

Honors-Awards
Clinical Manager
BSN Scholarship Winner 2019

Yolanda Rhodes RN, BSN, CRRN

Southwest Clinical Nurse Manager at BD Cypress, Texas

Summary

Experienced Clinical Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Neurological Disorders, Spinal Cord Injury, Traumatic Brain Injury, Admissions, and Nursing Documentation. Strong healthcare services professional and is a Certified Rehabilitation Registered Nurse.

Experience

BD

Southwest Clinical Manager May 2018 - Present (2 years 3 months) Houston, Texas

Experienced Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Neurological Disorders, Spinal Cord Injury, Traumatic Brain Injury, Admissions, and Nursing Documentation. Strong healthcare services professional and a Certified Rehabilitation Registered Nurse.

TIRR Memorial Hermann Clinical Nurse Liaison July 1999 - May 2018 (18 years 11 months) Houston, Texas

Assess and evaluate Spinal Cord Injury, Traumatic Brain Injury, Neurological, Neuromuscular and Orthopedic patients medical stability for transfer to acute rehabilitation. Initiation of discharge planning with patient and family prior to acute rehabilitation admission.

Education

The University of Texas at Arlington

Master of Science - MS, Nursing Education · (2018 - 2021)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor of Science - BS, Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2018 - 2020)

Lamar University

Associate's degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1993 - 1995)

Lamar University

Bachelor of Applied Science (BASc), Sociology · (1987 - 1992)